# Kostiantyn Bukhantsev

# JUNIOR FULL-STACK

#### SUMMARY

I am a Junior Full-Stack developer. I focus on HTML5, CSS3, JS, React, Node.JS and English. Development, practice and work for the result are important for me. I have hands-on experience in following Agile/Scrum methodology when working in a team. I am a fast learner, responsible, and ready for challenging tasks.

#### CONTACTS

- (**C**) +38(093)707-83-83
- 网 k.buhantsev@gmail.com
- GitHub
- (询 LinkedIn
- Odessa, Ukraine

# TECH SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS, Responsive/Adaptive design
- JavaScript
- · React Hooks & Components
- React Redux
- REST API
- Node.is
- MongoDB
- Parcel, Webpack
- Docker
- GIT

# SOFT SKILLS

- Analytical & problem solving skills
- Communication team
- · Ability to work in multiple projects
- Attention to detail

### LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

1C Developer (2011 - 2023)

2017 to current time: network of weapons shops «STVOL» 2016 - 2017 online store «Sunstones»

2012 - 2016 retail network «MD Group»

2011 - 2012 1C:Franchising «HVOYA-integra»

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

WebStudio [lin
A simple website with a responsive layout. Shows
basic knowledge of HTML and CSS. [HTML, SASS,
JS]
The state of the s

FoodSta ......[link] Responsive website with js-libruaries, svg-sprites

and other features. [HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel] Images finder [link]

Website implements images-API pixabay.com. [React]

Movies [link] Website implements films-API themoviedb.org. [React]

PhoneBook ...... [link front-end] [link back-end]

Phone book web application. You can register, log in, add, remove or filter contacts, log out. For its implementation were used following libraries: Material UI, React Hook form, React Router, Redux Toolkit, Redux Persist, Toastify, Yup, Prop-types and other. Server side is written on NodeJS. It realize user authorization, storing passwords and working with the contacts database. [React, Node.JS, MongoDB]

# EDUCATION

IT School GoIT (2022-2023)

Faculty: Fullstack Developer

**Udemy (2021-2022)** 

Faculty: JavaScript + React

**Odessa National Marine University (2005-2011)** 

Faculty: Shipbuilding, Specialization: Information technologies